<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>Hand-crafted</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products.</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>

  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Mojosoft Co., Ltd.</Company_Name>
    <Address_1></Address_1>
    <City_Town>Tokyo</City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code></Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>Japan</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://mojosoft.biz/</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_First_Name>Support</Contact_First_Name>
    <Contact_Last_Name>Team</Contact_Last_Name>
    <Contact_Email>support@mojosoft.biz</Contact_Email>
  </Company_Info>

  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>RocketMouse AI</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>2.0.1</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>03</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>31</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2026</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>199</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code>JPY</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other>29800</Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>No Install Support</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>macOS 14+</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Japanese</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Added AI Vision (Computer Use), Apple Intelligence integration, AI Autopilot, Self-Healing, 196 total operations. See release notes: https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/releases.html</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_Specific_Category>Productivity</Program_Specific_Category>
    <Program_Category_Class>Business::Other</Program_Category_Class>
    <Program_System_Requirements>macOS 14 (Sonoma) or later, Apple Silicon or Intel Mac</Program_System_Requirements>
    <File_Info>
      <File_Size_Bytes>88364411</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>86293</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>84.27</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Count>15</Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Other_Info>15-day free trial, full functionality</Expire_Other_Info>
    </Expire_Info>
  </Program_Info>

  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>mac automation, rpa, macos, browser automation, web scraping, playwright, excel automation, no-code, visual programming, block editor, ai automation, ai vision, computer use, apple intelligence, ocr, macro recorder, productivity, task automation, workflow automation</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Professional RPA automation tool for macOS</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>The first professional RPA tool built natively for macOS with AI Vision and Playwright</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>RocketMouse AI is the first professional RPA tool built natively for macOS. AI Vision (Computer Use) lets AI see your screen and click, wait, read, and validate autonomously. Features Apple Intelligence, Playwright browser automation, and 196 operations.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>RocketMouse AI is the first professional RPA tool built natively for macOS. AI Vision (Computer Use) lets AI see your screen and act autonomously — click buttons, wait for conditions, read text, and validate results by description alone. 196 built-in operations across 24 categories. Apple Intelligence on-device AI (free, no API key). Playwright browser automation, Excel, OCR, dual recording modes, visual element picker, breakpoints, and cross-platform .rmproj compatibility.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>RocketMouse AI is the most powerful visual RPA automation tool ever built for macOS. Snap color-coded blocks together to automate anything on your Mac — from browser tasks and Excel spreadsheets to file operations and screen recognition. No coding required.

Key Features:
- AI Vision (Computer Use) — AI sees your screen and acts: AI Click, AI Smart Wait, AI OCR, AI Validate, AI Autopilot, Bool AI Condition
- Apple Intelligence — Free on-device AI for the built-in assistant (macOS 26+, no API key needed)
- 196 Operations across 24 categories (Mouse, Keyboard, Browser, Excel, File, AI, Vision, and more)
- 6 AI Providers — Apple Intelligence, OpenAI, Anthropic, Google Gemini, Groq, Custom/Local LLM
- AI Autopilot — Autonomous agent loop using Anthropic Computer Use API (Sonnet/Opus)
- Self-Healing — When image/OCR fails, AI Vision retries with natural language
- Browser Automation — Playwright + Chrome built in. Navigate, click, fill forms, extract data. Visual element picker for CSS/XPath selectors
- Dual Recording — Input Recording (mouse + keyboard across any app) and Browser Recording (auto-captures Chrome interactions)
- Vision and OCR — Apple Vision-powered image recognition, template matching, and text extraction
- Excel — 18 spreadsheet operations, native file read/write
- Debug Tools — Breakpoints, step execution, variable watch, DryRun mode, speed control (0.1x-5.0x)
- Cross-Platform — .rmproj files are fully compatible between macOS and Windows

Built with Swift, designed for dark mode, Apple Notarized. Free 15-day trial.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
  </Program_Descriptions>

  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/pricing.html</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/images/og-image.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/images/app-icon-128.png</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/pad_file.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/download.html</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL></Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>

  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>Free to distribute the unmodified trial version.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>https://mojosoftjp.github.io/rocketmouse/license.html</EULA>
  </Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
